[Speaker_00]  Listen to the dialogue and practice your speaking, listening, and pronunciation skills.
[Speaker_00]  Hey Emily, how's it going?
[Speaker_01]  Hey Alex, great to see you.
[Speaker_01]  I'm doing well, thanks for asking.
[Speaker_01]  How about you?
[Speaker_02]  Not bad, just a bit busy with work lately.
[Speaker_02]  But I'm always happy to catch up with you.
[Speaker_00]  Me too.
[Speaker_00]  So, what's new with you?
[Speaker_01]  Well, I've been trying to get into gardening recently.
[Speaker_02]  Oh, that's cool.
[Speaker_02]  What have you been planting?
[Speaker_02]  I've started with some herbs like basil, rosemary, and thyme.
[Speaker_02]  And I'm also growing a few tomatoes and peppers.
[Speaker_00]  That sounds delicious.
[Speaker_00]  I've always wanted to try gardening, but I'm not sure I have a green thumb.
[Speaker_01]  Don't worry, it's not that hard.
[Speaker_01]  And it's actually quite relaxing.
[Speaker_02]  Plus, it's a great way to get some fresh produce.
[Speaker_00]  Yeah, I might give it a try.
[Speaker_00]  What else have you been up to?
[Speaker_01]  I've also been taking some online courses in photography.
[Speaker_01]  I've always been interested in it, and I'm really enjoying learning about different techniques.
[Speaker_01]  That's great. I've seen some of your photos on Instagram, and they're amazing.
[Speaker_02]  Thanks. I'm still practicing, but I'm getting better all the time.
[Speaker_00]  I sure you are What kind of photography do you like most I like to take pictures of nature in landscapes But I also interested in portrait photography
[Speaker_01]  I love nature photography, too.
[Speaker_01]  There's something so calming about being in nature and capturing its beauty on camera.
[Speaker_02]  I agree.
[Speaker_02]  And I find that portrait photography is a great way to capture people's personalities and emotions.
[Speaker_00]  That's true.
[Speaker_00]  So, what are your plans for the weekend?
[Speaker_01]  I'm planning to go hiking with some friends on Saturday.
[Speaker_01]  And then on Sunday, I'm going to visit my family.
[Speaker_02]  Sounds like a fun weekend.
[Speaker_02]  I'm going to a concert on Saturday night with my boyfriend.
[Speaker_02]  And then on Sunday, I'm just going to relax at home and catch up on some reading.
[Speaker_00]  Nice. I'm sure you'll have a great time.
[Speaker_01]  Thanks. I'll see you soon, Alex.
[Speaker_01]  See you later, Emily!
[Speaker_02]  To get into means to become involved or interested in something.
[Speaker_02]  It's like starting to participate in or enjoy a particular activity or hobby.
[Speaker_02]  For example, if you decide to get into hiking, it means you start to explore hiking trails and spend time outdoors enjoying nature.
[Speaker_02]  Capturing means recording or taking a picture of something, often to preserve a moment or image.
[Speaker_02]  It's like freezing a moment in time.
[Speaker_02]  For example if you capturing a sunset with your camera you taking a photograph to remember the beauty of the scene A green thumb is an idiom used to describe someone who has a natural talent or ability for gardening and growing plants successfully It like being skilled at nurturing and caring
[Speaker_02]  for plants, so they thrive under your care. For example, if someone has a green thumb,
[Speaker_02]  they can make even the most difficult plants grow beautifully.
[Speaker_02]  Let's listen carefully to the dialogue one more time.
[Speaker_00]  Hey Emily, how's it going?
[Speaker_01]  Hey Alex, great to see you.
[Speaker_01]  I'm doing well, thanks for asking.
[Speaker_01]  How about you?
[Speaker_02]  Not bad, just a bit busy with work lately.
[Speaker_02]  But I'm always happy to catch up with you.
[Speaker_00]  Me too.
[Speaker_00]  So, what's new with you?
[Speaker_01]  Well, I've been trying to get into gardening recently.
[Speaker_02]  Oh, that's cool.
[Speaker_02]  What have you been planting?
[Speaker_02]  I've started with some herbs like basil, rosemary, and thyme.
[Speaker_02]  And I'm also growing a few tomatoes and peppers.
[Speaker_00]  That sounds delicious.
[Speaker_00]  I've always wanted to try gardening, but I'm not sure I have a green thumb.
[Speaker_01]  Don't worry, it's not that hard.
[Speaker_01]  And it's actually quite relaxing.
[Speaker_02]  Plus, it's a great way to get some fresh produce.
[Speaker_00]  Yeah, I might give it a try.
[Speaker_00]  What else have you been up to?
[Speaker_01]  I've also been taking some online courses in photography.
[Speaker_01]  I've always been interested in it, and I'm really enjoying learning about different techniques.
[Speaker_01]  That great I seen some of your photos on Instagram and they amazing Thanks I still practicing but I getting better all the time
[Speaker_02]  I'm sure you are. What kind of photography do you like most?
[Speaker_00]  I like to take pictures of nature in landscapes.
[Speaker_00]  But I'm also interested in portrait photography.
[Speaker_01]  I love nature photography too.
[Speaker_01]  There's something so calming about being in nature and capturing its beauty on camera.
[Speaker_02]  I agree.
[Speaker_02]  And I find that portrait photography is a great way to capture people's personalities and emotions.
[Speaker_00]  That's true. So, what are your plans for the weekend?
[Speaker_01]  I'm planning to go hiking with some friends on Saturday.
[Speaker_01]  And then on Sunday, I'm going to visit my family.
[Speaker_02]  Sounds like a fun weekend.
[Speaker_02]  I'm going to a concert on Saturday night with my boyfriend.
[Speaker_02]  And then on Sunday, I'm just going to relax at home and catch up on some reading.
[Speaker_00]  Nice. I'm sure you'll have a great time.
[Speaker_01]  Thanks. I'll see you soon, Alex.
[Speaker_02]  See you later, Emily.
[Speaker_00]  Thank you.